So what's a feature? A feature can easily be thought of as a summarizer of something.
那么 什么是特征？ 简单点说 特征就是某个东西的归纳
So features of images are really just nice concise summarizes of image data.
图像的特征本质上就是图像数据的简要归纳
Furthermore, just as how images are really just a collection of numbers in an array,
此外 图像实际上可以看作一个阵列中的数字集合
features are also just another collection of numbers in an array.
同理 特征也可以看作一个阵列中的另一个数字集合
Although usually, they're much smaller than images.
但这个集合往往比图像的集合小得多
So what does this mean?
这是什么意思呢？
Let's be even simpler.
再简单点说
Forget images, consider humans.
我们不考虑图像 考虑人类
An individual person has many facets about
一个人有很多方面
themselves and it may be hard to fully describe someone in totality.
很难完整地描述一个人的整体
What are however some compact features that we may extract about a person?
但是 从人身上我们可以提取哪些简要特征？
Compact here because you want those features to describe something about this person,
简要是因为 你希望这些特征能描述这个人
but we want this description to be a summary of sorts to what is relevant.
同时描述应该是相关信息的概括
For example, if you wanted to place boxers into their weight class,
比如 如果你想把拳击手按体重分类
we may want to do feature extraction on each fighter and
我们可能会提取每个拳击手的特征
we would extract a two-dimensional feature, height and weight.
我们可能会提取二维特征 身高和体重
Those are features in the sense because of they nicely ignore the irrelevant.
这些数据可以叫特征 因为它们很好地忽略了无关信息
They described this person's weight and height.
它们描述了人的体重和身高
Features that are useful for placing the boxer into their proper weight class.
这些特征能有效地把拳击手归到正确的体重组里
They also ignore things like skin color or say hair length etc..
它们还忽略了一些信息 比如肤色、头发长度等等
So in this sense, you can think of feature extraction as a way to
因此 从这个方面来说 特征提取是一种
extract relevant information while also smartly ignoring the irrelevance.
提取相关信息、同时巧妙忽略不相关信息的方法
A good feature is always very succinct.
好的特征通常非常简明
Features are distinct and measurable pieces of information in an image.
特征是图像中鲜明、可测量的信息片段
And we'll go through examples of features and how to compute them.
我们会看一些特征的例子 以及如何计算特征
One of the breakthroughs in computer vision actually came from
计算机数据的一个重大突破 实际上就是来自
being able to automatically compute those features that are good.
能够自动计算好的特征
However, you can also do this on your own, manually.
但是 你也可以自己手动计算
In fact, you've already been creating your own features.
实际上 你已经创建了自己的特征
That's right. In the last exercise,
对的。 在上次的练习里
you had to come up with a distinguishing feature to classify
你必须得出一个区分特征
an image as taken during the day or night time.
对白天和夜间拍摄的图像进行分类
This feature was based on the overall brightness of the image.
这个特征是基于图像的总体亮度的
In this section, we'll see these features can be based on colors or shapes within
在本部分 我们可以看到 这些特征可以基于
an image and we'll see how
图像内部的颜色或形状 我们还会学习
these features can be used for obvious recognition and classification tasks.
如何将这些特征用于明显的识别和分类任务
Let's get started by talking about how features are used in industry applications.
首先 我们先学习如何在行业应用中使用特征